<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on console:portfolio</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on console:portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>RSS News Sentiment Analysis Dashboard</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/rss-news-feed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/rss-news-feed/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This project creates a daily-updated dashboard analyzing sentiment in news articles from various broadcasters. It uses RSS feeds to collect news data, performs sentiment analysis, and visualizes the results using a Streamlit web application.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jio - IKEA Notifications PoC</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/realtime-geolocation-notification/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/realtime-geolocation-notification/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;During my tenure as a data engineer at Jio Platforms, I was responsible for developing a proof of concept (PoC) pipeline and workflow tailored for two specific companies. This project involved collaborating closely with various stakeholders to understand their data requirements and business objectives. I designed and implemented a robust data pipeline that efficiently processed and transformed raw data into actionable insights.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The workflow I worked on demonstrates the integration of Jio&amp;rsquo;s telecom infrastructure with IKEA&amp;rsquo;s retail operations to create targeted marketing opportunities. By utilizing Label Switch Router (LSR) data for efficient network routing and geohash location determination, the system enables time-sensitive, location-based notifications to Jio subscribers near IKEA stores. This innovative approach aims to increase in-store sales, provide targeted incentives, and potentially boost revenue for both Jio and IKEA, showcasing the power of combining telecom data with location-based services to enhance customer experiences and drive business growth.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/introduction/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hugo is an open-source project and lives by the work of its contributors. There are plenty of open issues, and we need your help to make Hugo even more awesome. You don&amp;rsquo;t need to be a Go guru to contribute to the project&amp;rsquo;s development.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Hugo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/what-is-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/what-is-hugo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hugo is a fast and modern static site generator written in Go, and designed to make website creation fun again.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
